question_data = [{"category": "Geography",
                  "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "A group of islands is called an &#039;archipelago&#039;.",
                  "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The Southeast Asian island of Borneo is politically divided among 3 countries.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Science: Gadgets", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Microphones can be used not only to pick up sound, but also to project sound similar to a speaker.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "medium", "question": "E = MC3",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "Stagecoach owned &quot;South West Trains&quot; before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
